DYLAN PILGRIM

dylanpilgrim4746@gmail.com 07887 392016

I am a 23 year old post graduate, based in Leeds, looking to pick up full time work. I have experience working with the public in high pressure situations in teams and alone, I also have a positive attitude and am punctual without question.

Work Experience

HORTICULTURAL ASSISTANT

Robin Tacchi Plants. Norfolk

June 2022 - September 2022 June 2023 - August 2023

Robin Tacchi Plants is a plant nursery that focusses on the quality of plants over the quantity. Full time summer work, planting, transporting and caring for plants, in a team.

- Long hours
- Early mornings
- Physical work

BARISTA

Pepper's Tea Shop, Norfolk

July 2021 - September 2021

Pepper's Tea Shop is a tea / coffee shop serving drinks and food for local village residents. Full time summer work, making drinks, serving the public and keeping the shop clean.

- Serving customers
- Making drinks and serving food
- Keeping on top of cleaning and tidying

SHOP ASSISTANT

Onestop, Norfolk

November 2019 - July 2020

OneStop is a corner shop, offering an array of essentials for customers.

Full time work, serving the public and keeping stock under especially high pressure conditions.

- Long hours
- High pressure environment (during COVID 19 pandemic)
- Team player

GARDEN CENTRE ASSISTANT

Peter Beales' Garden Centre, Norfolk

June 2018 - September 2019

Peter Beales' is a garden centre offering a variety of plants and plant care products. Part time work, caring for plants and serving the public.

- Working with money
- Communication in teams
- Working alongside education

Prior work and references available upon request.

Education

BA (HONS) FILMMAKING

Leeds Arts University, 2021-2024

First Class Honours

Pre-university education results available upon request.

I hereby consent to the processing of the personal data in this CV by anyone who receives this CV for the sole purpose of consideration of my skills and experience for professional opportunities.